wordbanter.com 2016-05-12

# Microsoft Office Word Forum - WordBanter Privacy Statement

**Membership Information Collection and Use**  
Microsoft Office Word Forum - WordBanter is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from that disclosed in this statement. Microsoft Office Word Forum - WordBanter collects information from members at several different points on our website. 

**Registration**  
In order to best use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide some information (such as demographic information) but encouraged in order that we may provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about your registration with Microsoft Office Word Forum - WordBanter. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on this site. Once you close your browser, the cookie simply terminates. By setting a cookie on our site, you do not have to enter a password more than once, thereby saving time while browsing. You are not required to accept cookies to use this site although some features may not be available if you choose not to do so. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Advertising**  
In an attempt to help offset the costs of running this site, Microsoft Office Word Forum - WordBanter does accept some 3rd party advertising from responsible advertisers. No advertising is used which involves pop-ups, pop-unders, floaters, malware, adware, browser hijacks or homepage hijacks. Currently ads are being served by google. You can find their privacy details [here](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). If you become a registered user (which is free) you will not see any adverts in the main Microsoft Office Word Forum - WordBanter website. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Microsoft Office Word Forum - WordBanter. 

**Security**  
Microsoft Office Word Forum - WordBanter takes every precaution to protect your information. The server on which this site resides is administered by a commercial hosting company. Access to the server is restricted to trusted personnel and contained in a secure data center. If you have any questions regarding the security at our website, you can send an email to 

wordbanter@newsgroupbanter.com. 

**Site and Service Updates**  
We occasionally send you site and service announcement updates. During registration members are permitted to opt-out of these mailings. Should you choose not to receive these announcements, Microsoft Office Word Forum - WordBanter can not be held responsible for notifying you of any any changes made to this policy. 

**Correcting/Updating Personal Information**  
Your personally identifiable information is always accessible by you and can be changed at any time by visiting your profile page. If you no longer wish to be a member of Microsoft Office Word Forum - WordBanter, you should email wordbanter@newsgroupbanter.com to have your information permanently deleted from the site. 

**Notification of Changes**  
Notification of changes to our privacy policy are sent to members by way of email announcements. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. During registration members are permitted to opt-out of administrator mailings. Should you choose not to receive these announcements, Microsoft Office Word Forum - WordBanter can not be held responsible for notifying you of any changes made to this policy. 

**Archiving of posts**  
This forum archives posts from various newsgroups. It adheres to the 'X-No-Archive: Yes' standard in the headers of the post. If you wish you posts not to be archived on this or other archives which follow this convention, please use this in your message headers. More details relating to archiving of posts can be found at the faq's. If you request a post to be considered for removal, please email the url (web address) to wordbanter@newsgroupbanter.com together with the reason for removal.
